（口笛）
≪（通行人Ａ）
おい　あれ見てみろよ　あれ
Hey, look at her, man.
≪（Ｂ）うわッ　すっげー美人じゃん
モデルか何かか？
Whoa, she's really hot!
Is she a model or something?
Tachibana-kun!
（はるか）橘君！
（純一）すみません　森島先輩
遅くなっちゃって
S-Sorry I took so long, Morishima-senpai.
どうして？
時間ピッタリだよ
Huh? You're right on time.
でも　待たせちゃったから
But I made you wait...
そんなことより
早く行きましょう
Anyway, let's get going!
あッ…
My arm's touching her chest...
〈胸に　腕が…〉
≪（Ａ）もしかして　あれが彼氏か？
Is that her boyfriend?
≪（Ｂ）あんな美人と
つきあえるなんて　うらやましい
He's so lucky to be going out with such a hottie!
〈まさか　憧れの森島先輩と〉
Until a couple months ago, I never even imagined
I'd be dating Morishima-senpai, the girl of my dreams.
〈こうして　つきあえるなんて〉
〈２ヵ月前までは
考えられなかったな〉
うん？
何　私の顔に何かついてる？
Hmm? Is there something on my face?
いえ　そうじゃなくて
No, that's not it...
こうして森島先輩と
一緒にいられるなんて
I was just thinking how happy I am...
うんうん
すごく幸せだなって
Yep, yep.
...that we could be together like this.
Geez, when you say stuff like that,
I feel like making you even happier!
もう　そんなこと言われると
もっと幸せにしちゃうぞ
ほらほら　橘君　あれ見て
Hey, Tachibana-kun! Look at that!
キレイね
ですね
It's so pretty!
Indeed.
ねえ　橘君
はい
Hey, Tachibana-kun.
Yes?
いつ　私の両親に
会ってくれるのかな？
When will you come meet my parents?
出逢った瞬間
Deatta shunkan
From the moment we met
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
感じてた運命を 確信に変えたくて
Kanjiteta unmei wo kakushin ni kaetakute
I wanted to change this destiny I felt into conviction
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
plus
SS
Final8 presents
Amagami
＋
Final8 presents
Amagami
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
plus
Amagami
SS
＋
Final8 presents
plus
Amagami
Final8 presents
plus
Amagami
Final8 presents
plus
Amagami
今日も 君の傍に居るのかな
Kyou mo kimi no soba ni iru no ka na
I wonder if I can stay by your side again today
君の全てに
Kimi no subete ni
Everything about you
Check My Soul
ハートが動き出した
Haato ga ugokidashita
My heart begins to wake
今君と一緒に駆け出そう
Ima kimi to issho ni kakedasou
Let's break into a run together right now
Check My Soul
心の声聞いて
Kokoro no koe kiite
Listen to the voice in my heart
ゆこう この胸が高鳴る場所へ
Yukou kono mune ga takanaru basho e
Let's go to a place that will make my heart race
夢のような空間の中でも
Yume no you na toki no naka de mo
Even in dreamlike moments
真実だけを見つめていたい
Shinjitsu dake wo mitsumete itai
I only want to gaze at the truth
瞳の奥の
Hitomi no oku no
Inside your eyes
Check My Soul
心の声聞いて
Kokoro no koe kiite
Listen to the voice in my heart
ゆこう この胸が高鳴る場所へ
Yukou kono mune ga takanaru basho e
Let's go to a place that will make my heart race
Morishima Haruka
1st Half
Sexy
How daring of you.
（響）大胆ね　それで橘君は
何て答えたの？
So what was Tachibana-kun's answer?
別に何も　顔真っ赤にして
すっごく照れてた
He didn't say anything.
His face got really red and he was really embarrassed!
それが　またかわいかったんだけど
It was pretty cute, though.
そのときの様子が
目に見えるようだわ
I can imagine his face at the time.
≪（響）何か面白い記事でも
見つけた？→
Did you come across an interesting article?
Yeah!
イギリス特集？
A special on England?
This chapel...
このチャペル…
≪（響）これが　どうしたの？
What about it?
ここで　おじいちゃんが
おばあちゃんにプロポーズしたの
This was where my grandpa proposed to my grandma.
へえ　そういえば　はるかの
おじいさんはイギリス人だったわね
Ooh...
That's right, your grandpa's from England, isn't he?
うん
Yeah.
小さい頃は　よく聞かされたな
They told me a lot about it when I was young.
つきあい始めて　まだ半年も
たっていなかったんだけど
They'd been dating for less than half a year,
おじいちゃんが
いきなり　おばあちゃんを
but my grandpa just suddenly took my
grandma to the chapel and proposed to her.
チャペルに連れていって
プロポーズしたんだって
What's more, it was my grandma's graduation day.
しかも
おばあちゃんの卒業式の日に
≪（響）それは　すごいわね
That's amazing...
そのとき　一生仲よしで
いようねって約束して
They made a promise then to love each other forever.
I remember him telling me really happily
that's why they still love each other.
だから　今も仲よしなんだって
幸せそうに話してたのを覚えてる
あの頃　いつも
ジェシカと話してたな
I was always telling Jessica at the time how
I wanted a marriage like grandpa's and grandma's.
おじいちゃんと　おばあちゃん
みたいな結婚がしたいねって
≪（響）ジェシカって？
Who's Jessica?
あれ　言ってなかったっけ？
Oh, I never told you?
イギリスにいる　私の親戚で
She's my relative in England, Morishima Sexy Jessica.
森島・セクシー・ジェシカ
私より一つ年上なの
She's a year older than me.
へえ　セクシー…
R-Right, Sexy...
Jessica just graduated last year, but apparently
her boyfriend proposed to her on graduation day.
ジェシカは
去年　卒業したんだけど
その卒業式の日に　つきあってた
彼氏から　プロポーズされたんだって
その話を聞かされたときは
ちょっと　うらやましかったな
I was a little jealous of her when I heard about it.
はは～ん　それでデートのとき
So that's why you made Tachibana-kun look at wedding
dresses and asked him to meet your parents during your date.
橘君に　ウエディングドレスとか
両親に会ってくれとか
違う違う　プロポーズの話だって
さっき思い出したんだから
No, no!
I only remembered the whole proposing thing just now!
Really?
どうかしら？
Seriously, I'm not lying.
もう　ホントなんだってば
Though I'd be really happy if it did happen...
それは　してもらえたら嬉しいけど
でも　この話は橘君には内緒ね
But you're not allowed to tell Tachibana-kun!
何だか私から　おねだりしてる
みたいになっちゃうから
It'll make it look like I'm begging for it or something...
はいはい　あッ　橘君！
Yeah, okay.
Tachibana-kun!
ああ　森島先輩　塚原先輩
Morishima-senpai! Tsukahara-senpai!
T-Tachibana-kun!
橘君
What are you doing here?
どうしたんですか　こんな所で？
ちょっと響ちゃんと話しててね
I-I was just chatting with Hibiki-chan.
橘君こそ　どうしたの？
What about you, Tachibana-kun?
I stayed up late last night, so
I took a short nap at the infirmary.
ゆうべ　夜更かししちゃって
少し眠かったんで　保健室で仮眠を
そうなんだ
橘君　さっき　はるかがね…
I see.
Tachibana-kun, Haruka was just telling me-
ワーッ　ワーッ　響ちゃん！
どうしたんですか？
Hibiki-chan!
What's the matter?
...that she has a relative in England named Jessica who's one year older than her.
はるかには　ジェシカっていう
一つ年上の親戚が
イギリスにいるんだって
Oh, really?
へえ　そうなんですか
うんうん　そうなの
Y-Yeah, that's right!
それで　どんな人なんです？
So what's this Jessica-san like?
そのジェシカさんて人は？
えっとね　一つ年上で　女の子で
Let's see...
She's a year older than me, a girl and looks just like me!
私にソックリ
森島先輩に？
Just like you?
私を金髪で
緑色の目にした感じかな
Sort of like a me with blond hair and green eyes.
先輩を　金髪で　緑色の目に…
Senpai with blond hair and green eyes...
Hey!
That's awesome!
それは　すごいですね
あッ
えッ　何です？
Wh-What is it?
あのね
はい
You know...
Yes?
Do you have some time right now?
これから時間ある？
Japanese
Dictionary
Uh, what's this?
あの　これって…
予行練習よ　予行練習
A rehearsal, a rehearsal.
誰でも一度は通る道なんだし
はあ…
Since everyone will do this sometime in their lives.
Right...
はるかの考えてることは
何となく分かるけど
I kind of get what you're thinking, Haruka, but aren't you being a little too direct?
だからって　直接過ぎない？
Th-That's not it!
違います　いいから始めるわよ
Anyway, let's start!
（はるかが　結婚行進曲を口ずさむ）
仕方ないわね
I guess I don't have a choice.
えっと…
Uh...
あー　新郎・橘純一
はい！
The groom, Tachibana Junichi.
Y-Yes!
≪（響）汝は病めるときも
健やかなるときも→
Do you promise to love, cherish and devote yourself to
your bride, Morishima Haruka, in sickness and in health?
新婦・森島はるかを愛し　敬い
真心を尽くすことを誓いますか？
はい　誓います！
Yes, I do!
≪（響）新婦・森島はるか
はい
The bride, Morishima Haruka.
Yes!
≪（響）汝は病めるときも
健やかなるときも→
Do you promise to love, cherish and devote yourself to
your groom, Tachibana Junichi, in sickness and in health?
新郎・橘純一を愛し　敬い
真心を尽くすことを誓いますか？
誓います
I do.
Then I hereby pronounce you man and wife.
ではここに
二人が夫婦となることを認めます
じゃあ次は誓いのキスね
The wedding kiss comes next.
えッ！？
Hey!
や～ん
さすがに　それ以上は
Any more than that and we'd be crossing the limits of a rehearsal.
予行練習の範囲を超えているわ
No no, after the wedding ceremony, what obviously comes next is...
〈いやいや　結婚式が終われば
当然　次に来るのは〉
...the wedding night!
〈新婚初夜！〉
Come, Junichi.
《来て　純一》
《先輩…》
S-Senpai...
I'm pregnant!
できたって！
Huh? Uh...
えッ　あれ？　あの…
What about all the important stuff in between?
その前の重要なプロセスは？
うん　何？
Huh? What?
No, it's nothing...
いえ　何でも…
ねえ　はるか
うん？
Hey, Haruka.
確かに　私は
医学部に進学するけど
It's true that I'll be studying medicine in university,
産婦人科じゃなくて小児科志望
but I want to be a pediatrician, not an obstetrician.
どっちだっていいじゃない　子供を
相手にするのは変わらないんだし
Both are fine!
They both deal with young children anyway.
This is a scenario where the couple's at the hospital
for the first time after finding out the wife's pregnant.
今回は　赤ちゃんが
できたことが分かって
初めて夫婦で
病院に来たってシチュエーションよ
それじゃ　スタート
Okay, let's start!
先生　それで
私達の赤ちゃんの様子は？
Doctor, how's our baby doing?
Huh? Ah, uh...
えッ　ああ　えっと
順調ですよ
１２週目に入りました
E-Everything's going well.
You're twelve weeks pregnant.
We did it, darling!
やったわね　あなた
Darling?!
あなた！？
えッ？
N-Nothing!
頑張った甲斐があったよ！
A-All that hard work paid off!
Did he say "hard work"...?
頑張ったって…
ねえ　触ってみて
Hey, touch and see.
The new life we've created is right here inside me.
この中に　私達の
新しい命が宿っているのよ
先生　それで男の子ですか
女の子ですか！？
D-Doctor!
Is it a boy or a girl?!
えッ　あッ　えっと
Ah, uh...
女の子かな
A-A girl, I guess.
女の子か～
グッド！
A girl...!
Good!
結婚式　赤ちゃんときたら
Now that we've had the marriage ceremony and a baby, a family dinner's next!
次は家族団らんだね
ねえ　はるか　本当にやるの？
Hey, Haruka.
Are we really doing this?
やるの　打ち合わせしたでしょ
We are.
We already planned this out, right?
今日だけだからね
Just for today, okay?
それじゃあ　夕方　お父さんが
帰ってきたところからね
Well then, let's start from when the
dad comes back home in the evening.
Okay, start!
はい　スタート
I-I'm home.
ただいま
お帰りなさい　あなた
Welcome home, darling.
Hibiki, you need to welcome your papa home as well.
ほら　響もパパに
お帰りなさいしなさい
Come on, Hibiki.
ほら　響
P-Papa, w-welcome homesies!
パパ　お帰りんりん
えッ　お帰りんりん？
Huh? "Welcome homesies"?
パパなんて
実の親にも言ったことないのに
"Papa", seriously?
I've never even called my actual dad that...
さあ　お食事の用意ができてるから
食べましょう
Well, darling.
Dinner's ready, so let's eat.
今日はデラックス定食よ
It's the deluxe set today!
おお　豪勢だな
Ooh, what a feast!
I'm digging in!
（三人）いただきま～す
Darling, open wide!
はい　あなた　あ～ん
あ～ん
Is it good?
どう　おいしい？
うん　おいしいよ！
Yeah, really good!
じゃ　ママにも
はるかって呼んで
Mama gets some too.
Call me Haruka.
はるかって呼んでくれなきゃ
食べてあげない
I won't eat if you don't call me Haruka.
えッ！？
呼んで！
Say it!
No, but like, that's...
あッ　いや　でも　それは…
That's what?
それは？
ちょっと　恥ずかしいというか
Kind of... you know, embarrassing...
You're no fun!
そんなのつまんない
よくそれで
ママと結婚できたね　パパ
It's a wonder how you got Mama to marry you, Papa.
By the way, you never told me.
そういえば
聞いたことなかったけど
パパは　何て言って
ママにプロポーズしたの？
What did you say to Mama when you proposed to her?
〈響ちゃん　ナイス〉
Nice one, Hibiki-chan!
Hey, what did you say?
ねえねえ　何て言ったの？
Uh, I...
えっと　それは…
それは？
You what?
内緒
エーッ
It's a secret!
What?!
アハハハハ…
あの　森島先輩
プンだ
Um, Morishima-senpai?
Hmph!
また今度
続きをやりましょうね
Let's do the rest another time.
フン
Hmph.
You should probably have a proper
proposal ready the next time we do this.
次にやるときは　ちゃんと
プロポーズの言葉は
考えておいた方がいいかもね
ちょっと　響ちゃん
H-Hey, Hibiki-chan-
Hi!
（ジェシカ）ハ～イ！
J-Jessica?!
ジェシカ！？
It's been so long, Haruka!
久しぶりね　はるか
What are you doing here?
どうして　ここに？
はるかの顔を早く見たくて
I couldn't wait to see you!
会えてラッキーね
いつ日本に来たの？
I'm so lucky to see you here!
When did you arrive in Japan?
今日よ　ついさっき着いたばかり
Today.
I just got here!
〈本当に　そっくりだ〉
They really do look alike.
あんまり変わってないわね
はるかは
You haven't changed very much, Haruka.
ここの大きさも
Including how big you are here!
ちょっと　やめて
ところで　こっちの二人は？
Hey, stop that!
By the way, who are these two people?
同級生の塚原響ちゃんと
２年生の橘純一君よ
Tsukahara Hibiki-chan, my classmate and Tachibana Junichi-kun, a junior.
Ｎｉｃｅ　ｔｏ　ｍｅｅｔ　ｙｏｕ！
ナイストゥーミーチュー
Nice to meet you!
N-Naisu to meechu.
よろしくね　響　純一
Let's get along, Hibiki and Junichi!
はじめまして
どうも
Thank you.
Th-Thanks.
〈森島先輩もすごいけど
さすが外国の人〉
Morishima-senpai's are amazing,
but this person really is a foreigner...
何か？
あなたが　はるかの彼氏ね
Wh-What is it?
You must be Haruka's boyfriend.
話に聞いていたとおり
ベリーキュート
Just like what she said, you're very cute!
W-Wait, Jessica! What are you doing?!
ちょっと　ジェシカ　何してるの！？
何って　ただの挨拶よ
Huh? It's just a greeting.
それは分かってるけど
I know, but...
ここは日本なのよ　少しは考えて
We're in Japan, remember?!
オ～　ソーリーね
Oh, sorry!
でも　どうして日本に？
So why are you in Japan?
I'm here to attend your graduation
ceremony and do some sightseeing.
はるかの卒業式を見に来たの
それと日本観光
何も　わざわざ来なくても
You didn't need to take the trouble to come...
だって　彼氏ができたんでしょ？
But you got a boyfriend, right?
おばあちゃんとか
私みたいに　卒業式に…
Just like grandma and me, maybe he'll-
ワーッ　ワーッ　ワーッ！
どうしたんですか　先輩？
What's wrong, Senpai?
ああ　虫　虫がいたの
Oh, a bug. There was a bug!
もう春だからかな…
It's already spring, after all.
Ah, looks like it went away.
シー
Phew...
ヘイ　純一
はい！
Hey, Junichi.
Y-Yes!
頑張りたまえよ　日本男児
Do your best, Japanese guy!
ああ　はあ…
Uh, okay...
もうジェシカったら　橘君には
内緒なの　言っちゃダメなの
Geez, Jessica!
You can't tell Tachibana-kun! It's a secret!
どうして
まずいことは何もないでしょ？
Why not?
There's nothing wrong with telling him.
まずいわよ　もし言っちゃったら
催促したみたいになるじゃない
There is!
It'll look like I'm asking for it if I tell him!
I asked my boyfriend for it.
私は彼にお願いしたわよ
私は　あなたと違うの
I'm different from you.
オー　つまんないよ　せっかく
卒業式前に彼氏ができたのに
Oh, don't be such a bore!
You even managed to get a boyfriend before your graduation, so...
言っておきますけど　そのために
つきあい始めたんじゃないの
Just saying, but that's not why we started dating.
たまたま　その
It's just that... well...
好きになったタイミングが
そうなっただけで…
I happened to fall in love with him just in time for it...
分かってる　はるかは　そんな
器用なタイプじゃないもんね
I know.
It's not like you're shrewd enough for that anyway.
でも彼は　あのこと知っているの？
But does he know about the whole thing?
ううん　話してない
No, I didn't tell him.
もう時間がないんだよ
分かってる
You're running out of time.
I know.
でも…
But...
〈それにしても　そっくりだったな〉
But man, Morishima-senpai and Jessica-san really look alike.
〈森島先輩と　ジェシカさん〉
（美也）にしししし　ねえねえ
にぃにも見てよ
Hey, Nii-nii, look at this too!
今回も　すっごく面白いよ
Beaver
Three Kingdoms
This volume's really funny!
「ビーバー三国志」最新刊
It's the newest installment of Beaver Three Kingdoms!
何　どうしたの　にぃに？
Huh?
What's wrong, Nii-nii?
〈もし美也に
金髪で緑色の目をした〉
If there was a lookalike of Miya
with blond hair and green eyes...
〈そっくりさんがいたら…〉
《ヘイ　まんま肉まん
ベリーおいしいネ！》
Hey!
Meat buns, very delicious, man!
《いっぱい　いっぱい
アイキャンイートだよ》
I can eat lots and lots of them!
《Ｎｉ　ｓｉｓｉｓｉｓｉ！》
いや　これはないな
Nah, I don't think so.
えッ　読んでもないくせに
何それ！？
What?! But you haven't even read it!
もういいよ　にぃにには
見せてあげない
Fine, then! I'm not letting you read it.
I'm here to attend your graduation ceremony.
《はるかの卒業式を見に来たの》
Graduation, huh?
〈卒業か　先輩　卒業したら
大学に行っちゃうし〉
Senpai will go to university after she graduates.
〈そうすると　会える時間
減っちゃうよな〉
That would mean we'll have less time to see each other...
It'll be pretty lonely when that happens.
〈やっぱり寂しいな　そうなると〉
あッ　森島先輩！
Morishima-senpai!
あれ？
Huh?
Morishima-senpai.
森島先輩
はッ！
ああ　橘君か　ビックリした
O-Oh, it's you, Tachibana-kun.
You scared me.
すみません
ううん　考えごとしてたから
I'm sorry.
It's fine, I was thinking about something.
それで　何か用？
いえ
What do you want?
Well...
特に用というわけでは
ないんですけど
Nothing really, I just wanted to say hi.
そう
I see.
Huh? Morishima-senpai seems down.
〈あれ　森島先輩　元気がない〉
〈やっぱり卒業しちゃうから
寂しいのかな〉
Could she be feeling lonely that she's about to graduate?
〈いや　もしかしたら　昨日のアレが
途中で終わっちゃったから…〉
Or maybe it's because we stopped that game halfway yesterday...
先輩
何？
S-Senpai.
What?
もしよかったら
昨日の続きをやりませんか？
If you'd like, should we continue where we left off yesterday?
もちろん塚原先輩も誘って
We'll invite Tsukahara-senpai too, of course.
あれ　ダメですか？
Uh... You don't want to?
Um, I'll think about it.
う～ん　ちょっと考えておく
じゃあまたね　バイバイ
I'll see you later. Bye-bye!
（梅原）森島先輩が　いつもと違う？
Morishima-senpai isn't quite herself?
うん　何か変なんだよ
Yeah, something's strange.
それはやっぱ
卒業しちゃうからじゃねえか
It's probably because she's about to graduate, right?
やっぱり　そうなのかな？
So that really is it, huh?
いざとなりゃあ　どんな人でも
感傷がわいてくるってもんさ
Hey, man.
Anyone would feel sentimental when the time comes.
かな～？
（薫）何々　純一　フラれたの？
I dunno...
What's up? Did Junichi get dumped?
フラれてないよ！
No!
How about taking out your seething
frustrations on some part-time work?
その衝動を
バイトにぶつけてみない？
ちょうど人手も足りないとこだし
We just happen to be short of people.
だから　フラれてないって！
Like I said, I wasn't dumped!
（梨穂子）純一
おう　梨穂子
Junichi!
Oh, Rihoko.
聞いたよ
森島先輩にフラれたんだって？
I heard that you got dumped by Morishima-senpai.
How about healing that gap in your heart by
joining the Tea Club and having some delicious tea?
そんな心の隙間を　茶道部に入って
おいしいお茶で
癒やされてみない？
ちょっと待てよ
別に僕　フラれてないぞ
W-Wait!
I didn't get dumped or anything!
えッ　そうなの？
Oh, really?
But rumors are flying around that you got dumped by Morishima-senpai.
でも純一が　森島先輩に
フラれたって噂になってるよ
It must be Kaoru.
薫のヤツだな
Tachibana Junichi-kun of Class 2-A.
[ｽﾋﾟｰｶ]２年Ａ組の橘純一君
電話が入っています
You have a call.
Huh? You have a call, Junichi.
あれ　電話みたいだよ　純一
誰からだ？
Who's it from?
Excuse me.
S t a f f   R o o m
すみません
Hello? This is Tachibana.
もしもし　橘ですが
[TEL]（ジェシカ）ハロ～
その声は　ジェシカさん？
Hallo!
Is that... Jessica-san?!
ワオ　昨日会ったばかりなのに
よく分かったわね
Wow!
I'm surprised you could tell even
though we only just met yesterday!
[TEL]電話口でハローって挨拶する
知り合いは　他にいませんから
I don't know anyone else who'd greet me with a "Hallo!" over the phone.
Good, I'm glad we can skip the pleasantries.
[TEL]うんうん　話が早くて助かるわ
どうしたんですか　わざわざ
学校に電話してくるなんて？
Why'd you take the trouble to call the school to reach me?
私ね　これから少し
輝日東を離れるの
I'll be away from Kibitou for a while.
憧れの京都観光　いいでしょ
I'm going sightseeing in Kyoto!
Cool, right?
[TEL]はあ
でも　話の本題は　それじゃないの
Right...
But that's not what I called you for.
そう…　なんですか
I... see.
[TEL]はるか　寂しがってるよ
えッ？
Haruka's feeling lonely.
[TEL]イギリスにね　はるかのことを
There are plenty of guys in England who love her.
[TEL]好きだって言ってる男の子が
たくさんいるの
[TEL]ロビンでしょ　テリーに
ステアに　いじめっ子のニール
There was Robin, Terry, Stea and Neil the bully...
はあ
あんまり寂しい思いをさせると
Right...
Haruka might be taken away from
you if you make her feel too lonely!
はるかのことを
さらっていっちゃうかもよ
だから頑張ってね　橘純一君
So do your best, Tachibana Junichi-kun!
[TEL]えッ　あの　それって！
Wait, what do you mean-
ウフフフ
橘君
Tachibana-kun.
どうしたの　こんな所で？
What are you doing here?
橘君！？
T-Tachibana-kun?!
ねえ　どうしたの？
Hey, what's wrong?
橘君？
Tachibana-kun?
どうしたの　何か変だよ
What's the matter? You're acting weird.
先輩！
はい！
S-Senpai!
Yes?!
僕　先輩のこと大好きですから！
I-I really love you, Senpai!
イギリス男なんかに負けませんから！
I won't lose to those England guys!
I won't lose to Robin, Terry, Stea or Neil the bully!
ロビンにも　テリーにも　ステアにも
いじめっ子のニールにも負けません！
先輩にも　寂しい思いは
させませんから！
I won't make you feel lonely!
フフフッ　そっか
ジェシカに聞いたのね
I see, so Jessica told you.
けど　それは子供の頃の話
でも！
But that was back when I was a kid.
B-But...!
橘君
はい！
Tachibana-kun.
Y-Yes!
Know this.
これだけは信じて
私は橘君のものだから
I belong to you, Tachibana-kun.
先輩…
S-Senpai...
This place brings back memories.
ここ　懐かしいわね
ああ　はい　そうですね
Yes, indeed it does.
先輩？
あのとき　すごくくすぐったかった
Senpai?
It was really ticklish, you know!
ヒザの裏にキスされて　しかも
止めるまで　ずっとしてるし
You were kissing the back of my knee...
And you didn't stop until I told you to!
ハハハ　すみません
Sorry.
でも　先輩のヒザの裏は　すごく
スベスベしてて気持ちよかったです
The back of your knee was really smooth and felt really good.
Geez, there you go again...
もう　また　そういうこと言って
そういえば　まだ聞いてなかった
何をですか？
Oh right, you never got back to me.
On what?
あのとき　犬の気持ちが
分かるかもって言ったじゃない
Well, you said you'd probably be able to understand why dogs do that, right?
あれから何か分かった？
What did you learn from it?
Uh... I'm almost there.
えっと　もうちょっとなんで
もう一度すれば
はっきり分かるかも
Maybe I'll know for sure if we do it again.
Nope!
ダメ　あんなくすぐったいこと
２回もできません
I can't do something that ticklish a second time!
ハハハハッ　ですよね
I guess so.
でも　よかった
But I'm glad.
また　ここに来られて
I'm glad we could come here again.
思い出の場所だから
We made memories here, so I wanted to see it one last time before I graduated.
卒業する前に　もう一度
見ておきたかったの
思いがけず　それがかなっちゃった
My wish unexpectedly came true.
先輩…
Senpai...
最初はビックリしちゃった
I was really surprised at first.
だって　何も言わずに
手を引いていくんだもの
I mean, you just took my hand and pulled me without saying anything.
すみません　何ていうか　その
Sorry.
How do I say this...
My feelings got all worked up...
気持ちが
高ぶっちゃっていたもので
ウフフフ　いいわ　許してあげる
It's fine. I forgive you.
〈よかった
いつもの先輩に戻ったみたいだ〉
Good thing she seems to have returned to her usual self.
森島先輩！
Morishima-senpai!
うん　何？
What?
今度
Do you...
今度　僕の家に遊びに来ませんか？
Do you want to come over to my house sometime?
えッ…
朝を運ぶバイクの音が
Asa wo hakobu baiku no oto ga
The sound of bicycles each morning brings
僕に時間の流れ告げ
Boku ni toki no nagare tsuge
Tells me of the passage of time
もうどこへも行けない気持ち
Mou doko e mo ikenai kimochi
My feelings have nowhere else to go
君に渡す覚悟決めた
Kimi ni watasu kakugo kimeta
I've decided to tell you about them
未来に散りばめた 予定は隣に 君がいてほしい
Mirai ni chiribameta yotei wa tonari ni kimi ga ite hoshii
I want you right by my side in my plans for the future
息を吸って吐き出す
Iki wo sutte hakidasu
I take deep breaths in and out
言葉は幾度もため息に変わるけど
Kotoba wa ikudo mo tameiki ni kawaru kedo
My words keep turning into sighs
伝えたい言葉はただひとつだけ
Tsutaetai kotoba wa tada hitotsu dake
But there's just one thing I want you to know
好きだよ
Suki da yo
"I love you"
僕の告白
Boku no kokuhaku
It's my confession
Preview
次回　予告！
Next episode preview.
It's the first time I got invited
to Tachibana-kun's house.
橘君の家にご招待されちゃった
ご招待しちゃいました
I just couldn't help inviting you.
どんな風に　ご両親に
挨拶したらいいかな？
So how should I introduce
myself to your parents?
えッ？
Huh?
両親は仕事で帰ってこないので
Um, my parents will be away because of work, and Miya's staying over at her friend's place...
美也も友達の所に泊まるとかで
ふ～ん　そうなんだ
はい
Oh, I see.
Yes.
橘君のエッチ
えッ！？
Tachibana-kun, you pervert.
What?!
次回「タビダチ」
橘純一　男を見せます！
Next Episode
Morishima Haruka
2nd Half
Next Episode
Morishima Haruka
2nd Half
Next Episode
Morishima Haruka
2nd Half
Departure
Next episode: "Departure".
I, Tachibana Junichi, will be a man!